Labor Song Books 5189
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Labor Song Books
1935-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
5189
2.33 cubic feet
2.3 linear ft.
Publications, song books.
Includes various issues of the Little Red Song Book of the IWW.
8209406
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 09, 2007
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 08, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections:
Working class v Songs and music; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Library; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives; Industrial Workers of the World
8209406
- AFL-CIO song book (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  [Washington, D.C., 1957?]-4 copies
  - Item 1: AFL-CIO song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: AFL-CIO song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By AFL-CIO. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: AFL-CIO song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By AFL-CIO. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: AFL-CIO song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By AFL-CIO. Copy 4. Item is in English.
- The ACTWU song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  [New York, N.Y.: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1978?]-6 copies
  - Item 1: The ACTWU song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The ACTWU song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Amalgamated songbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  New York: distributed by Education Department, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America-CIO, [19-- ?]
  - Item 1: Amalgamated songbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Education Department. Item is in English.
- America Sings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  [U.S.: s.n., 193-?]
  - Item 1: America sings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Item is in English.
- Arts and crafts for the recreation leader, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  New York, National Recreation Association, [1941 c1936]
  - Item 1: Arts and crafts for the recreation leader, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Frank A. Staples. Item is in English.
- Parties for special days of the year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  New York, National Recreation Association[1943]
  - Item 1: Parties for special days of the year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Ethel Bowers. Item is in English.
- Parties, musical mixers and simple square dances, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  New York city, National Recreation Association [1943]
  - Item 1: Parties, musical mixers and simple square dances, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Brookwood Chautauqua songs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  New York: Brookwood Labor Publications, [1936?]
  - Item 1: Brookwood Chautauqua songs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Brookwood College. Item is in English.
- Song-book, Bryn Mar summer school, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Song-book, Bryn Mawr summer school, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Bryn Mawr College. Item is in English.
- A century of songs, 1852-1952, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  [S.I.: New York State Electric and Gas, n.d.]-3 copies
  - Item 1: A century of songs, 1852-1952, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: A century of songs, 1852-1952, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A century of songs, 1852-1952, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Copy 3. Item is in English.
- CIO song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Washington, D.C.: CIO Dept. of Education and Research, [195-]-2 copies
  - Item 1: CIO song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Department of Education and Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: CIO song book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Department of Education and Research. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- CIO songs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Birmingham, Ala.: Birmingham Industrial Union Council, [19--]-2 copies
  - Item 1: CIO songs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: CIO songs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- The C.O.L.A. songbook, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  S.I.: Cornell Organization for Labor Action, 1978
  - Item 1: The C.O.L.A. songbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cornell Songs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Cornell Songs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    2 leaves. Item is in English.
- Twice 55 games with music, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Boston: C.C. Birchard, 1924
  - Item 1: Twice 55 games with music, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Peter W. Dykema. Item is in English.
- Everybody sings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  New York: The Union, 1942, 1947, 1951, -3 copies
  - Item 1: Everybody sings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Everybody sings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Everybody sings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Songs of work and freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Chicago, Roosevelt University 1960, & New York: Dover Publications, 1973-2 copies
  - Item 1: Songs of work and freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Edith Fowke. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Songs of work and freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Edith Fowke; Joe Glazer; Kenneth Bray; Hope Taylor. Item is in English.
- Games file for clubs, families, camps, church, parties, outings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Pittsburgh, PA., Published by Workers' Section of the Group Work Division, 1957
  - Item 1: Games file for clubs, families, camps, churches, parties, outings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    By Group Work Division. Item is in English.
- Handbook for recreation leaders, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Washington, U.S. Govt. Print. Off., 1936-2 copies
  - Item 1: Handbook for recreation leaders, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Ella Gardner. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Handbook for recreation leaders, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Ella Gardner. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Free labor sings.-Chants du travail libre, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Bruxelles: International Labour Film Institute, Institut International des Films du Travail, Internationals Institut fur Arbeiterfilme
  - Item 1: Free labour sings. - Chants du travail libre, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Labor Arts presents Songs of the Wobblies, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Detroit: Labor Arts, 1953 - 2 copies
  - Item 1: Labor Arts presents Songs of the Wobblies, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Joe Glazer; Bill Friedland. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Arts presents Songs of the Wobblies, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By Joe Glazer; Bill Friedland. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Trade union songs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Washington, D.C.: The American Federation of Labor, n.d.
  - Item 1: Trade union songs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    By Annabel Lee Glenn. Item is in English.
- A handbook for UAW-CIO recreation leaders, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Detroit, UAW-CIO, 1944
  - Item 1: A handbook for UAW-CIO recreation leaders, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Melvin G. West. Item is in English.
- Battle hymns of toil, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  [Oklahoma city, Okla.: General Welfare Reporter, 1945?]
  - Item 1: Battle hymns of toil, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Covington Hall. Item is in English.
- Sing a song of unsung heroes and heroines, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  University Park, PA,: Dept. of Labor Studies, Pennsylvania State University, 1986
  - Item 1: Sing a song of unsung heroes and heroines, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Alice M. Hoffman; Tom Juravich; Franklin W. Russell. Item is in English.
- The Rebel Girl, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  New York: Glad Day Press, [1915]- 2 copies
  - Item 1: The Rebel Girl, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Joe Glazer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Rebel Girl, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By Joe Glazer. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Worker of the world awaked, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Worker of the world awaken, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Worker of the world awaken, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Don't take my papa away from me, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Chicago, Industrial Workers of the World, [1916]
  - Item 1: Don't take my papa away from me, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Joe Hill. Item is in English.
- Labor songs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  New York: Textile Workers Union of America, c1939 - 6 copies
  - Item 1: Labor songs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Zilphia Horton. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor songs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Labor songs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- the ILGWU songbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  New York, NY: International Ladies Garment Workers' Union, [1989]
  - Item 1: The ILGWU song book, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ILR song sheets, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: ILR Song sheets, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
- In the factory, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: In the factory, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    One song from ILGWU, not a collection, and not bound. Item is in English.
- The International: One big Union [IWW], Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The International: One Big Union [IWW], Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    One song (words and music). Item is in English.
- We have fed you all a thousand years [IWW Song book], Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: We have fed you all a thousand years [IWW Song book], Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Part of a bigger song book. Item is in English.
- The Labor Heritage songbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Washington, D.C.: Published by the Labor Heritage Foundation, n.d.
  - Item 1: The Labor Heritage Song book, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- IWW Song books, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Contains 11 song books, 10 of which are restricted
  - Item 1: Songs of the workers on the road, in the jungles and in the shops, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Workers of the World. RESTRICTED. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Songs of the workers on the road, in the jungles and in the shops, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Songs of the workers on the road, in the jungles and in the shops, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Songs of the workers on the road, in the jungles and in the shops, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: I.W.W. songs: songs of life, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Songs of the workers: to fan the flames of discontent, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: I.W.W. songs: songs of life from the mine, mill, factory and shop, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Workers of the World. (22nd). RESTRICTED. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: I.W.W. songs: songs of life from the mine, mill, factory and shop, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Workers of the World. (21st). RESTRICTED. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Songs of the workers to fan the flames of discontent, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: I.W.W. songs: songs of the workers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: I.W.W. songs: songs of life: and "take out the words, if so must be, but leave, oh, leave the melody.", Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Workers of the World. (18th). RESTRICTED. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: I.W.W. songs: songs of life: and "take out the words, if so must be, but leave, oh, leave the melody.", Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Workers of the World. (18th). Copy 2. RESTRICTED. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: I.W.W. songs: songs of life: and "take out the words, if so must be, but leave, oh, leave the melody.", Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Workers of the World. (17th). RESTRICTED. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: I.W.W. songs: songs of the workers., Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Workers of the World. 2 copies. RESTRICTED. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: I.W.W. songs: songs of the workers., Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 16: I.W.W. songs: songs of the workers., Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 17: Songs of the workers: to fan the flames of discontent, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 18: Songs of the workers: to fan the flames of discontent, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Workers of the World. Copy 2. RESTRICTED. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Songs of the workers on the road, in the jungles and in the shops, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Sing along songbook, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  [Ithaca, NY: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1993]
  - Item 1: Sing along songbook, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Labor sings, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  New York: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1940
  - Item 1: Labor songs for all occasions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Let's sing! (2d ed), Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  New York City: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Educational Dept., [n.d.] - 2 copies
  - Item 1: Labor sings, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Let's sing (1st ed.), Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  New York City: International Ladies' Garment workers' Union, Educational Dept., [1953]
  - Item 1: Let's sing! (2d ed), Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Let's sing! (2d ed), Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Let's sing! (2d ed), Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Let's sing! (1st ed), Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Let's sing! (1st ed), Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Let's sing!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kentucky square dances, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Louisville, KY., Recreation council, c 1928
  - Item 1: Kentucky square dances, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Ida Levin. Item is in English.
- On the line !: songs for social change, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  [Toronto, Ont.: "On the Line" collective, 1983]- 2 copies
  - Item 1: On the line !: songs for social change, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Arlene Mantle. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: On the line !: songs for social change, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Arlene Mantle. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Sing a labor song, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  New York, N.Y.: Gerald Marks Music, Inc. 1950 - 4 copies
  - Item 1: Sing a labor song, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By Gerald Marks; Milton Pascal. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Sing a labor song, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By Gerald Marks; Milton Pascal. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Sing a labor song, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By Gerald Marks; Milton Pascal. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Sing a labor song, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By Gerald Marks; Milton Pascal. Copy 4. Item is in English.
- Recreation in a labor setting, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Detroit: [International Recreation Dept., United Automobile Workers-CIO], 1949
  - Item 1: Recreation in a labor setting, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    By Ruth March. Item is in English.
- Midwest Workers' Education conference. 1946, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Midwest Workers' Education Conference, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Homes play in wartime, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  [New York, c1942]
  - Item 1: Home play in wartime, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    By Virginia W. Musselman. Item is in English.
- singing farmers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Denver, Colo: National Farmers Union, c1947
  - Item 1: Singing farmers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Harry Robert Wilson. Item is in English.
- Original railroad songs from the film Convention One, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  [U.S.A.]: Harold Mayer Productions, Inc., c 1972
  - Item 1: Original railroad songs from the film Convention One, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
- People's songs wordbook [no. 11], Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  New York: Peoples songs, 1947
  - Item 1: People's songs wordbook [no.1], Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Picket line songs, Local Union 489, Amalgamated Clothing Workers, Andalusia, Alabama, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  [Andalusia, Alabama: Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1947]
  - Item 1: Picket line songs, Local Union 489, Amalgamated Clothing Workers, Andalusia, Alabama, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Sit down sister!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  [s.l.: ILGWU, 1937]
  - Item 1: Sit down sister!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By Fall River, ILGWU. Item is in English.
- Sing along the way, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  New York, NY: The woman's Press, n.d.
  - Item 1: Sing along the way, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Socialist Sunday school song book, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Brooklyn, N.Y.: Brownsville Socialist Sunday School, [192-?]
  - Item 1: Socialist Sunday school song book, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Songbooks, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  contains two songbooks. One from ILGWU and another from The Washington Assembly
  - Item 1: Songs, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Washington Asembly's - 7 Songs to Freedom, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
- The songs of Joe Hill, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  New York: Oak Publications, 1960 - 2 copies
  - Item 1: The songs of Joe Hill, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    By Joe Hill; Barrie Stavis; Frank Harmon. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The songs of Joe Hill, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    By Joe Hill; Barrie Stavis; Frank Harmon. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Songs for labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  1983. 2 copies and mimeographed copies. AFL-CIO
  - Item 1: Songs for labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Songs for labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    By Education Department. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Songs for labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    By Education Department. mimeographed copies. Item is in English.
- Socialist and labor songs of the 1930s, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Chicago [ILL]: Charles H. Kerr Pub. Co., 1997
  - Item 1: Socialist and labor songs of the 1930s, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By Elizabeth Morgan; Ernest Morgan; Utah Phillips. Item is in English.
- Songs of struggle, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  missing from folder
  - Item 1: Songs of struggle, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    missing from folder. Item is in English.
- Songs our union taught us, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  New York: Educational Dept., International Ladies' Garment workers' Union, [19--]
  - Item 1: Songs our union taught us, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Song book of the pacific coast school for workers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Berkeley, Calif,: Pacific Coast School for Workers [1939]
  - Item 1: Song book of the pacific coast school for workers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    By Caroline Wassermann. Item is in English.
- Songs of the people, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  New York, Workers Library Publishers, [1937] - 2 copies
  - Item 1: Songs of the people, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Songs of the people, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Red song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  New York: Workers library publishers, [c1939]
  - Item 1: Red song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Songs for America, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Which side are you on?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Washington, D.C.: United Mine Workers of America, [between 1986 and 1988] - 2 copies
  - Item 1: Which side are you on?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Which side are you on?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Ye olde time favorites, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  s.l.: United Transportation Union, n.d.
  - Item 1: Ye olde time favorites, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Songs of the Southern School for workers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Asheville, N.C. :s.n., 1940
  - Item 1: Songs of the Southern School for Workers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Steelworkers' song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Pittsburgh, Pa.: United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO-CLC[195-?] - 2 copies
  - Item 1: Steelworkers' song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Steelworkers' song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
- TWUA songs, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  [New York, n.p. 1948] - 3 copies
  - Item 1: TWUA songs, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: TWUA songs, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    By Education Department. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: TWUA songs, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Songs, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  New York, Textile Workers Organizing Committee, n.d.
  - Item 1: Songs, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
- TWUA songbooks, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Includes two different songbooks.
  - Item 1: TWUA songs for action, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: TWUA-CIO songs for union hall and picket line, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: TWUA-CIO songs for union hall and picket line, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: TWUA-CIO songs for union hall and picket line, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Textile workers song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
- This Land is Your Land- songs of Social Justice, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  not online, not enough to catalog, just one sheet of lyrics - 3 copies
  - Item 1: This Land is Your Land - Songs of Social Justice, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    just one sheet of lyrics. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: This Land is Your Land - Songs of Social Justice, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    just one sheet of lyrics. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: This Land is Your Land - Songs of Social Justice, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    just one sheet of lyrics. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- UAW-CIO songs: Sing!, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Detroit, Michigan: UAW-CIO, International Education Department, n.d. - 2 copies
  - Item 1: UAW-CIO songs: Sing!, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    By International Education Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: UAW-CIO songs: Sing!, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    By International Education Department. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- URW songbook, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Includes two different song books. Akron, Ohio.
  - Item 1: URW song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: URW song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Workers song book: no. 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  New York: Workers Music League (U.S.A. Section of International Music Bureau), 1934
  - Item 1: Workers song book: no. 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
- folder of song sheets, collections, etc., Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: folder of song sheets, collections, etc., Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Single sheet/song, or a collection for a specific conference, nothing in book form. Item is in English.
- the ILGWU song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  New York, NY: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, [1989]
  - Item 1: The ILGWU song book, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Pins and needles with ILGWU players, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  New York: Mills Music, c1937
  - Item 1: Doing the reactionary: Pins and needles with I.L.G.W.U. players, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    By Harold J. Rome. Item is in English.